In previous episodes of Everwood
Nina told me what you did
And I said that you kissed
Jake, I am sorry
What can I say?
There is nothing you can say
Because now we are no longer friends
I do not know many things about music and I do not know ..
What were talking about here, but
Whatever it is, is working
Is very pleased to these lessons
-- Reid came on about?
-- Yes
It was sitting beside me, and before I
Rendessi account ... I kissed
Oh my God!
-- There can believe
-- I am delighted for you
Now I have no time to tell
But finish between 10 minutes
Wow
There seems to be past
A truck here
Delia and I have made biscuits
Until late
I spent the last 10 minutes
Trying to think
A way to fix this disaster
I do not think so a disaster
You should see my house
Yes
Lathes at home?
No, I have come to do laundry
Very well, you still see more now
When were living here
It is because the laundries are costly
To that serve? Also ....
There are always long file
Ephram
I think there is something I should tell you
Ah si? What?
Well, I think that should tell you ...
However, I am not sure ...
It 'just something that I heard around but
I think you should know
Dad
I think that Amy is coming out with a boy
What?
I heard that he was telling that to Hannah
A boy had kissed
Even if I know that a kiss
Does not necessarily mean "go out together"
No, I think ...
This may not be true
We talked about this the other day,
Have misunderstood
Maybe, but one thing is possible
But perhaps I asked
If he was going out with someone and I said no
It is not going out with anyone, so ...
Okay, perfect
I I am wrong,
May have misunderstood
Yes
But I did well to tell you is not true?
-- Yes, of course
-- Very good
And 'late, we
Only 7:15
We must leave now because
I arrive early at school
We must organize many things
Before beginning the lesson
Let's go!
Can you skate?
Pattinare? I grew up in California.
I grew up on a scooter
Of course I know skate ...
Fantastico
Be nice
Good morning
Hello! How is Jake?
Yesterday night we did biscuits
Yes?
Oh my God. They look fantastic
I am for school
It 'been very tiring
Pasta is very difficult
I know
I wanted to call but dad told me
They would have fared the same
I thought it was the time to prove
This oven so modern that I bought
Well, are perfect
Feeney!
Arrive late
We go there
Hasta luego!
Hello boys
See
"Free Fall"
Have you seen my shoes basketball?
They could be here, but
There is no way to know
Hey, no need to clean
I can not do without, I know
That very soon will be as before
And that I should not do this, but I can not
Stay here without doing anything
Do not feel a strange smell?
I think that there is something rotten
My smell has atrofizzato
Forced to stay here so long
Well, the game
Closed more or less at 4
We call ends well when we put ourselves in agreement
Very good
Yes ...
I see?
And 'This is the beauty of having a boy
Know where it is
And you know that you will call
Reid kissed me by one week
And yet I have no news
And do not even know where he is
Is not even here,
This is not his apartment?
In this regard,
You are somewhat 'exaggerating
The you must stop continue to come here
To wait in his apartment
What did you intend to say
If enter by that door?
I do not know
Excellent ...
I need to know if
Disappeared
Or if I am avoiding
Even 5 minutes
So if you still end up crazy for
I just want to know what is happening
Be in ignorance kills me
You know if Bright saw Reid?
May be dead
Or hospital or something like
What?
Yes, but these things happen sometimes?
Why this may not be a good reason
That a boy not calling you?
Maybe you should call
And ask him to leave
I never asked to leave
To a boy
And if I say no?
It would be very embarrassing
Not you say no!
Has kissed ...
It is clear that the piaci
And if that kiss was only
A momentary weakness?
Who knows? And not ever know if
I shall give to be done to find out
Okay, there is only one way to
Know
I think it is not hiding
In his apartment until they return home
You are right we should leave
From here immediately
We
Move, move, move
I was thinking about it
Various' more ....
Think this is too
Eh?
Oh, no, no
Why this piece I
Was doing crazy
And 'too long
And unequal, that is better
Yes something like
Okay you happen?
You are as absent
No, I have nothing, I
Only thinking about one thing
I have made no comments that
That happened in New York
You are right, you are still surprised that the fact
You know even laugh
I was beginning to worry
The application for admission to Juilliard
I am like crazy,
In a few months
Go to the best
Conservatory of world
What?
Nothing
Have you ever completed a question?
Yes
Okay
Then know that you can not fill
An application with the pencil, no?
And 'only a rough draft, after
I will write to pen
00:07:16,854 -> 00:07:18,106
Oh, well, good idea
You are jealous of me
I go there
While you stay here
To give lessons to the losers
Listen
This does not mean entries to Juilliard
The chances are minimal
You must be aware and do not want
That your life twist
Around this because,
Madness, I was there
And it's not so easy
It may be that you do not come, but
Both know that I am a genius
I agree genius
Dimostralo
Perfect
-- Hey
Have you tried our
New salad?
I do not like the prickly
On seriously? And 'very tasty
Really? So I think
Try the
Harold me is waiting
Oh Andy, you have a minute?
I must tell you one thing
Of course, what would happen?
Really you want to say it
For a long time
The problem is that
I know that I have not taken the
Your bid
To be friends
And the fact is that I want to do
But I do not know how
Or better, but I know how ...
You have been my best friend for so long
And we are still friends, but ...
I do not know how comportami with Jake
I mean ..
I do not know what to do
-- Must seem a stupid
-- No, all is well
I really enjoy seeing that, for once,
Are you that man
This is a nonsense
I feel like themselves
At school and my boy
Prohibiting me from talking to other kids
And what do you think?
I want to be back
Andy friends
I want to continue to do
Cookies with Delia
But at the same time
I do not want to hurt Jake
And I thought you should talk
To solve the problem
I already apologized into post
And almost sent me to the devil
I know but maybe you should
Try again
But if he does not want to stay even
In the same room with me
Do you think it will be prepared
To sit down and talk?
I do not want to believe
That all this has no solution
No, it is not true that there is no solution,
It's just that it is complicated
But will do my best
If you like
-- Will it really?
-- Certainly
Well
Well, fantastic
I deal with Jake and
Then how to take care of
You know where to find me
Eating the prickly
Not so awful these curtains?
Incredible
Someone must know
Our card number
Have picked a sum
Significant moment ago
11,000 US dollars
On behalf of "Extreme Adventures"
That the devil is this?
And why they needed
A sum so disproportionately?
Maybe it is somehow degenerated
Watching pornographic sites
Or playing at Black Jack-online.
And this is Bright
-- Rose, what the number of boy?
-- Harold
I was I
You?
You have bought pornography?
While waiting
TAC results ...
I booked a trip to Africa
Do not worry, I have already cancelled
There ridaranno money
In a few days
Africa? Why?
It was when ...
I was back cancer
I would like to
One last trip with the whole family
So you were safe
You are about to die?
Yes
Part of me was safe
I have never said anything
The thought continually
And I am sure that even you thought
And I said
Okay ...
Now we can talk
Six alive, you are good ...
The world is yours
Have you thought about what you now?
Truly, I am not sure
I have not thought about nothing concrete
The last thing that I thought
Was the fact of losing their job
You will find another job, I am sure
A person was
Driving this city
Fighting with a multitude of crazy
Can do whatever he wants
With Treasury
But in the meantime I devote
To prepare delicious meals
I am 10 years accumulation recipes
Speaking
I should choose one for tonight
I made seven operations today
And four of them came
Affixed from Denver
There are doctors in Denver?
Yes but no surgeon in Los Angeles
One of these days
End up working for Jessica Simpson
You are very kind treasure
I think that you could make it more beautiful
Believe that we have not understood
Who do not even know who is?
Well ... I was thinking
Since they have only two weeks
Fair weather
We should invite
Brown for a barbecue
It 'a good idea
Now not see them very
What do you think Jake?
Then see
But we do the shopping
And tell him in advance
Let's not go into now
Why should we leave?
I had already planned are only two people in more
Yes, because we can not?
Yes why?
Let Sam, I
You see something
But we have not finished
Yes, but you will see is a lot of fun
Thanks to the trap
I am sorry
But I did not know how to do that.
We talk about this thing
-- Talking about what?
-- By Andy
This morning in the car not
You even said hello
So? Now am I bad?
No, of course not
The fact is that there must be a disservice
In this story
I want to be friends torniate
I do not think it is possible, I do not want
Be a friend Andy Brown
But yes I
And not only with him but with the whole family
Well, I do not know what to say
Your relationship is strong enough
The situation could worsen
It seems to me very difficult
I know that is difficult, but this
Means a lot to me
Why is it so important for you?
Try something for him?
No, of course not!
It 'just that I lack
Delia saw every day
After school
And she always played with Sam
And I do not want to feel guilty if you knock
At the door in front to take a coffee
Try to sforzarmi
Various' more with Andy, okay?
You know?
What do you think if take
An appointment with a therapist?
Sorry?
I know, I know that one thing is crazy,
But can work
I have no intention of doing therapy with Andy
There even think to therapy
It is not a therapy
Is a mediator
In your conversation
I think we could achieve alone
Yes, I would like to see what happens
When you start talking
Risolverete all in 5 minutes
And everything will remain exactly the same
Andy is ready to do so, however
If you do not feel ready ...
Please
I am in Los Angeles, I began
To make therapy 6 years
Start to get around
Not then there has never imported anything of this
You and Andy were friends, remember?
Yes, this happened before you baciasse
This is only to speak with him
I must really love you so much
For her, Miss Feeney
I will do
Amy
-- Reid
-- Hello
Hello
Did I not tell you seen lately
Yes, I know ... I was
Covered work
Oh, I am sorry
No. I think the best time to ..
Make social life
Is not a week that stop ...
Study and
I still do 20 pages
Tomorrow
I think that is an idea fogliettini
Bad it is not true?
I do not believe that
To my future patients
Would like this thing
Probably not
Then assume that you will be busy
Even the night
Really ...
Friday are free
Want to do something?
Friday?
Yes, of course
Fantastic, is a spectacle on campus
We could go back to see how
Yes, I would like
Okay
Please call us so we agree
Fantastic, OK, we see
-- Friday night
-- Agreed
Oh, hello
You intend to squagliartela?
What? Of course not
I wanted to see because ...
Bright has said that Friday
There is a concert of "The Killers"?
"The Killers"?
Yes, playing in the city and if
We want to go to the concert
Will be better to take tickets now
I wanted to know if you went
To come with me or something like
I would like
But to tell the truth I can not,
I
Why? And 'why exit
With someone?
I am sorry, do you think this is not strange to talk about these things?
Yes that is
We should not talk about this?
No, we can certainly
No matter, I am happy for you,
Is fantastic
-- Thanks
-- Yes
Can we go again
See the concert
Yes, of course, when you want it
-- Okay
Should ...
Okay, hello
What is this?
Oh, nothing special,
It is only a list
They are potential jobs
You might do
It 'a very long list
There are at least 52 options
I am proud
To have found so many
The field ..
Social services
Opens an enormous number
Opportunities
Lawyer?
Why not?
It 'a great opportunity.
You are restarting from scratch
It 'time to give the right proverb
And reach for the stars
I do not know what to say
I do not expect this
Do not be afraid Rose
I am here to offer
All my support
And advise, do not leave
Sink in the crisis of 50 years
I had not realized
To be to sink
Indeed
Can withstand the problem of 50 years
Maybe, but not us too custody
For a woman of your age
And the house empty
Is not very difficult
Fall into depression
And also have lost their jobs
The community offers assistance
For women without work
Health aids ...
Psychological support
For people who need it
I see
And I thought that having to rest
Having had cancer
And you must, but I do not want
Adagi and you lose your skills
I am here
I talked to Jake and I took appointment
Tomorrow for a session
What?
Yes, I am a genius
We love Leslie
Who is Leslie?
Well, is the friend of a friend
Usually dedicated
Treatment of pair
But I told your situation
And has agreed to come and
Help you talk
You have contacted a consultant marriage?
No, I have not contacted
She does as Please
Is a friend of a friend
Scordatelo, I do not believe that I and Jake
We need a consultant, really?
I thought that you did everything necessary
Yes, but I did not imagine having to
Do therapy pair with your boyfriend
That certainly is not my boy
What do you want Andy?
I am doing a lot of effort and trust
It is not at all easy
But there I am trying
Because it is very important to me
And what should we talk?
It is rather 'strange not believe?
I sat Jake ...
Talking about you ...
"Leslie the therapist?
I do not see why it would be strange
Because there is nothing romantic
Among us
No, of course not
I was referring to this ...
And this is only to clarify
Some misunderstandings?
Yes, I think so
Damn, I will
You are the best
Then we see tomorrow
At 12 o'clock
There I will be
Ay Pope
More plan
-- I am not running
-- Do you run. More plan
If sound plan, go into coma
Make a break
Okay
And so ... The brontolone is back
Dimenticami
It would, however, so that at Juilliard
Admit only people happy, and then ...
Do not go to Juilliard
Since when?
We soon a pen for your question?
-- The devil Vai
-- Yes, the problem is ..
It is evident that there
Something that concerns you
Fartelo try to say some 'time
But it will take a long time
Will be better than
I say without wasting time
The application for admission is 100 US dollars
And I do not owe this money
It 'a lot of money but ...
You can not do anything?
It 'easy to find 100 US dollars
What work is your father?
-- It 'a surgeon
-- It 'clear, is not a doctor any. It 'a surgeon
We regret if you say something?
Tell me
You rich not think things
And believe that people
Not have problems earning money
I did not say this
My mother earns $ 15 per hour
And many costs
How can ask 100 US dollars?
I rider in face
-- Can I give you the money
-- No, I need your love
It is not charity,
It 'a loan
No, it is
Already I doing free lesson
You can not ask too
Would be pathetic
And if I
Accepted to Juilliard
How am I going to pay
Plane tickets?
EI books?
Calmati, there is still time
-- We take care after
-- This thing will not work
Kyle
Do not go to Juilliard
Why do we continue to talk about this?
In any case I thank you
There was fantastic l 'last part?
-- I thought I was dying
00:22:21,155 -> 00:22:23,184
Reid, how are you?
And 'my companion biology
Yes?
Want something to eat?
And 'late and I hunger
Truly, I much work
Be done
And I promised to finish
Before tomorrow
It's OK if I go?
Yes, Vai
So you accompany home
Okay
-- What are you doing here?
-- Also welcome to me to see you
I stopped,
Fired six
Truly, you can not dismiss
Someone who does not pay. Courage
-- Not playing
-- Okay
Then suonerai
We
Do not have anything better to do?
Close your mouth and salts by car
Just in time
Arriving late is a peculiarity
My character
Leslie Hammen, this is the
Dr. Andy Brown
-- Pleasure
-- How are you?
I am ready
-- We
-- Okay
We go to the movies, have fun
We will do treasure
There is nothing more fun
To do therapy with another man
Sarcasmo. Interesting
Aspects. I did not know that this had
Count all Andy
What you referring to?
Are you referring to something?
00:24:09,074 -> 00:24:10,574
The do - you
And if you continue this way, you
Better position not even the jacket
-- This is stravincere want ..
-- I see? E 'want stravincere
Do not see who is on the defensive?
I think it frightened
Good luck Leslie
We go. Hello boys
Usually start talking
Sexual problems
But it is clear
That is not the problem
I was accompanied at home at 9,
Embraced me and he went
Such appointment ...
Ceni if there?
No, if you have not touched
-- Bright!
-- I scoppier his head
No. I have never felt so confused by
The behaviour of a boy
You have just washed a glass?
Yes, it is all that I need
Maybe we should do the hard
No, you say that it's over
It was not even started
Yes Bright
And now it's over
The fact is that ...
I do not know what to think ...
Kisses me and not ask me
Even leave
-- Yes you asked to leave
-- I mean really quit
And 'true. Did not
We went to see a show
Practically we have not talked
Oh my God
Maybe when I have not had rice
And he thought it was strange
No, I am sure not.
You know when to laugh
Thanks
But no longer important,
It is finished now
Vado he
Hello
What happens?
Dai go. Are you ready?
Hello Reid
What happens?
Nothing special, exit the library?
Yes, step so much time there,
I should pay rent
Well then ...
We see
Really?
Only "we see?
What?
Did piaccio?
What? Certainly
No, no, no, I am asking you if you piaccio?
Because sincerely,
So confused ... I kissed you
I have not had your news
Until we had an appointment
I have not asked you
But now I do not understand what is happening,
Really do not know
Or maybe yes,
Because what happened last night ...
Has been a disaster
Really?
I was good
Yes?
Yes
So why you involve so?
Why am I waiting 4 hours of study
Amy, you know ...
As is the stressful
The first year of medicine?
You know?
I very piaci
But is that all life dream
Become a doctor
I knew that it would be difficult
But can sleep
Only 4 hours a day
I do not have time to have a girlfriend now
Yes, even I want a boy hour
Fantastico
Because now I only time
For something ...
Informal
And if you do not want, I understand
No, it's not that I do not want
That is not so ...
Which means "informal"
All my previous reports
Has been set ..
From the beginning
Even my
Is that ..
When you leave with someone at school
Things seem more serious
But now ...
We are at university
And people simply ..
Is "fun"
But I am not suggesting you
To do so
I think we face some 'fear the idea
To be alone
Yes but who knows?
It can be the same fantastic
Have someone with whom
Divide things
But keeping your
Freedom. Think
You know?
It is very important to know what
You are doing in your life
I do not want to sound condescending, but ...
What you want to do
University?
Take a degree
But still I do not know what
Okay. Do not worry,
Discover the
But I know what I do not want, do not want
Finally, as my mother
Do not get me wrong.
She is incredible
It is
It 'just that I do not want the
Typical bourgeois life
I understand?
Why must already decide
How will your life Amy?
Now I have to go to study
But ...
You call this week goes well?
Believe that nature
Solve my problems?
In part
I do not think that works
Do not have 16 years
Why not you relax
And take advantage?
Beginning to behave like my father
At what age you played
The plan for the first time?
Watch you should talk
If you walk with me
Or this will be the longest day
Your short life
At 6 years
And it was at home o. ..?
My father bought me a "Casio" e. ..
And I started playing this thing
Only did it experiments but ...
Okay, are you?
When did you start?
My mother bought me my first
Piano when I was 4 years
-- Let's see if I guess .. A "Grand"?
-- A "Baby Grand"
We sold when he died
And we went away from New York
Oh
How many years had died when?
Almost like me now
Yes
You grew up in New York?
Yes we moved here
Some years
At first I gave nuisance
But now no
New York is why
I want to go to Juilliard
-- Ah yes?
-- Yes
There are a lot of people
Can I go and do what I want
Without that someone intrometta
In my business ...
Who intromette?
Your mother?
And then that business can have you?
These bikes can be hired e. ..
We can get off the mountain with these
OK, I am not going to do this thing
Why?
Wow
I do not want to get off the mountain
Nor should you
Thanks to worry about me
I worry because you need
Bring home
We can go back
I think it is better
You are here
-- You talked about working with the museum?
-- Still no
Do not sleep Rose, Jobs
They are not alone, courage
Harold, I am not your project or
A child who asks help with the tasks
Why call them "children"
If they are not children?
-- You are very strange. It's OK?
-- No, no good
Yesterday frightened me greatly
With talks on the crisis in 50 years
And the fact that I was sinking
, And now want to work as volunteer
As if I wanted to save
I understand you scared the idea of entering another time
In the labour market
But it is perfectly normal
But we are here to help me,
We together every step
What steps?
What do you think that should only choose
Work from your list and try?
Harold, I just had a cancer and
I have absolutely no idea what I will do
If you want to know what is happening to me,
I feel completely lost and hysterical
I feel as if I had to climb
A mountain without knowing what's behind
-- Yes, however ...
-- If you want to talk work stopped
I have lost my job,
I made my family suffer
Which is the most important thing in my life
-- Very well, and what will?
-- No. know, this is the problem, do not know
And your attempts to help
Are only worsening the situation
E 'was the reason why
You have not submitted to the hearing Jiuliard?
In reality is somewhat 'more complicated,
But basically, yes
-- Ed is the same reason that has ruined the week?
-- No, no, no, it is different
And I will not ruin anything,
Only disturbs me
And 'This is why I did not
The girl is too stressful
It 'difficult enough resolve your problems
If then add others.
-- Do not think that sometimes you can help others?
-- No
In the end it's nice to have someone
Where to go when everything goes wrong
-- The play?
-- No. know
-- There should be a man with the smoking why?
-- I do not see
Continue to play
When I look back, I realize
That it was a mistake
-- When we think ..
-- A "mistake"?
Who does these things? Go back to my woman
When we assume that we are friends?
-- With all due respect. He was my friend before
-- And this gives you the right to kiss?
No, I have just said that it was a mistake
I am sorry, really.
And if I could I would erase it
You can continue to say these things, but I think
That you would do exactly the same thing
I do not know that answer,
I have just said that I would not
Jake
Jake Listen, if you think that you can not
Resolve this situation, we do not believe ...
What we do here?
I do not believe. I understand.
But if you do not accept my apologies ...
-- You are an imbecile
-- Have you heard?
He heard what I said?
And not criticized ...
Or something like that?
This is not constructive
He behaves as if it were that good,
Reasonable, but is not
Baciarla was not a mistake.
You are correct!
Believe that you can have it all.
What you just take it.
I bet you believed that I do not
I have had opportunities with Nina if you had the desired
The first surgeon
Youngest nation
Cover of Time, Why not?
And when you tired,
Become bucolic ...
You move into a picturesque country
And open a free study
And when this does not seem sufficient,
Sometimes works
Vai the devil Jake! I have given everything
To become what they are
I have sacrificed everything! My family ...
The relationship with my wife ...
And we should not even speak of this!
We should talk about Nina!
-- What does all this mean?
-- It has nothing to do with Nina!
-- So that cock factor?
-- No. know
I believed was right for you,
But this is not the case
I think it is for what ...
You represent
What you and
I will not
Listen Jake, you are doing
Things right
Can you reconcile work and family
As I have never managed to do
Not spend 10 years
Domandandoti because you just
Or because you kissed a woman
That would have had to kiss
Trust me.
Did all is well
Unless you want playing the piano
You can explain why six
Finished playing the hotel?
-- I wanted to try it with the ladies
-- Yes, for this and for the money
-- Even for this
-- How much you earn?
-- 50 US dollars
-- It is not evil, just missing you
I know
Very well. Take this
I will give you a check for the rest
-- Thanks
-- There are people who pay the lessons
You quit rinfacciarmelo eh?
No, we will remember all my life
See you Thursday?
So?
Jake says that it went well
How was yours?
Well
-- The truth is that it has been a success
-- Thank God
Do not get me wrong,
But not at all easy to see
I know that we have been friends
For a long time
But I really do not
That would have passed in a session
In fact, the reason why it went well
Is that cares deeply for you
It could not go that well
Thanks Andy
To tell the truth
I feel honoured
Two men lottino for me ..
I was never successful
Those who have not lotterebbe for you?
I see? You always right
Thanks
If this is a different list of works,
Go escandescenza
It is not, it is a journey
Remember that you deleted safari?
I booked again
For the two of us
-- Harold
-- I know the territory Masai
-- What?
-- Yes, it was always my dream ...
Since little when I read
My first "National Geographic"
I was deeply impressed
-- And what happens about the search for my future?
-- You reason
We can not force the situation,
Or choose a career from a list
We will try everything,
As they say young people
It must play hockey at least once
In life, make small hours sometimes
What happens when you return?
It will be all the same
This is not safe
It may be that we will see things from
A 'other perspective, who knows?
With some 'luck, we inspiration
And if it will not, at least we will have done
A fabulous trip
Do not worry Rose
The exceed
And then you want to make this trip
Because you thought that you would be dead
But we will do to celebrate
The fact that continue to live
You know? I think that my perspective
Has already changed
Really? In what sense?
I just discovered what is the thing
Best to defeat cancer
And spend more time with you
The best way to mix pizza
You do so
I can not believe that you do know
Yes, I learned when I was working
In the restaurant
How goes with Reid?
Continue?
Yes, for the moment
It's fantastic, my god ..
Is so beautiful
-- Hey! Your boy is here
-- Not saying to me is good to Amy
What do now?
I do not know, we have not decided anything
Maybe we see this
Weekend o. ..
Perhaps not, I do not know yet
Is informal
You know that this means?
Truly yes
But it is perfect, I do not feel like now
Have another story intense
Hey!
There are distributors of pizza?
Bright is an expert impastatore
They are expert in all
When you might notice it?
-- Want to lend a hand?
-- Sure
Very well. Get. Remove this
You seem happy
Yesterday I spent a wonderful day.
I took the chairlift and I climbed on top of the mountain
Looks fun
But some six 'great for these things
Yes, go so long with a boy
For 15 years, ends up contagiarti
Feeling wiser and believe
To be able to influence in his life
Translation: HBK
00:32:00,903 -> 00:32:04,771
And a volunteer in the museum or
Studying law, will not change the situation
00:00:0,500 -> 00:00:2,00
www.tvsubtitles.net